William N. Fenton Papers 1933-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.20
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1897-1994; 39 boxes; 19.25 linear feet
  - Herrick, Jim W., 1972 (Box Series I-16)
  - Herscher, Irenaeus, 1968 (Box Series I-16)
  - Herskovitz, Melville J., 1944-1962 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hertzberg, Alvin, 1949 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hertzberg, Hazel W., 1967-1988 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hertzfeld, Regina Flannery, 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Herzog, George, 1933-1950 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hetrick, Bernard, 1946 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hetzel, Theodore, 1970 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hewitt, J.N.B., 1934-1937 (Box Series I-16)
  - Heye, George G., 1940-1945 (Box Series I-16)
  - George G. Heye Foundation, 1991 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser. IIa, Museum of the American Indian, Heye Foundation
  - Heyerdahl, Thor, 1962 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hibben, H.J., 1939 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hickerson, Harold, 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hickerson, Nancy Parrott, 1978 (Box Series I-16)
  - Higham, Charles F.W., 1974 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser. I, Somerville, Jack S.
  - Higham, Tom, [1975?] (Box Series I-16)
  - Highwater, Jamake, 1976 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hilger, M. Inez, 1957 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Cephas D., 1934-1956, 1975 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Charles (Mrs.), 1943 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Dorothy, 1944 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Hilton, 1940-1944 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Ike (Mrs.), 1943 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser. I, Jamieson, Sadie
  - Hill, Isaac, 1941 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, James C., 1987-1988 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, Joseph (Box Series I-16)
    -See Ser. I, Schneider, L.E.
  - Hill, Scotty Isaacs, 1943 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hill, W.W., 1942 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hilton, D.B. (Box Series I-16)
  - Hinchey, Maurice D., 1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hinke, William J., 1940 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hinman, Marjory B., 1967 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hinsley, Curtis M., Jr., 1982 (Box Series I-16)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania, 1949 (Box Series I-16)
    -See also Ser. I, MacCallum, Spencer
  - Hitti, Philip, 1945 (Box Series I-16)
  - Hobbs, Ranald P., 1943-1946, 1990 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hochschild, Harold K., 1964-1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hockett, Charles F., 1947-1948 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hodgen, Margaret T., 1953, 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hoebel, E. Adamson, 1946-1953, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hoffman, Daniel, 1961 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hofmann, Charles, 1948, 1966 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hogg, David A., 1938 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hoijer, Harry (Box Series I-17)
  - Holder Press, 1947 (Box Series I-17)
  - Holland, Nina, 1981 (Box Series I-17)
  - Holmberg, Allan R., 1950 (Box Series I-17)
    -See also Ser. I, American Ethnological Society
  - Holmer, Nils M., 1948-1949 (Box Series I-17)
  - Holmes, Harry A., 1947 (Box Series I-17)
    -See also Ser. I, Blaker, Margaret C.
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1959-1972 (Box Series I-17)
    Bailey, Nicodemus
  - Holt, Josephine M., 1953-1956, n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Holt, Philip J., 1987 (Box Series I-17)
  - Holt, Rinehart, & Winston, Inc., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Home, Ruth M., n.d. (Box Series I-17)
  - Homet, Marcel, 1947 (Box Series I-17)
  - Honigmann, John J., 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Honyoust, John, 1946 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hooks, Edward, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hopkins, Vivian, 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Horák, Jirí, 1962 (Box Series I-17)
  - Horn, Francis H., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Horowitz, Gary S., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Horowitz, Michael M., 1971 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hotchkiss, Nancy (Box Series I-17)
  - Hough, A.F., 1939 (Box Series I-17)
  - Houghton, Ruth M., 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1959-1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - Howard, James Henri, 1969-1974 (Box Series I-17)
  - Howard, Oscar, 1941 (Box Series I-17)
  - Howgate, James C., 1945, 1969 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hoxie, Frederick E. (Box Series I-17)
    -See Ser. I, Newberry Library
  - Hudacs, John, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-17)
    Reilly, Joseph M.
    Walkley, Frank
  - Hudson, Charles Melvin, Jr., 1966-1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hudson, Joyce Rockwood, 1976 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hughes, Charles C., 1953, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
    Smith, Jeffrey A.
  - Human Relations Area Files, Inc., 1950, 1968, 1992 (Box Series I-17)
    Martin, Marlene
  - Humphrey, Bill, 1985-1986 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hunt, Charles (Box Series I-17)
    -See Ser. I, City of Liverpool Museums
  - Hunt, George T., 1940, 1947 (Box Series I-17)
    Gulzeth, Irene
  - Huntington, W. Chapin, 1947 (Box Series I-17)
  - Huntington Free Library and Reading Room, 1979 (Box Series I-17)
  - Huntington Library, 1945-1994 (Box Series I-17)
  - Huot, Martha Champion (Box Series I-17)
    -See Ser. I, Randle, Martha Champion
  - Hurl, G.E., 1943 (Box Series I-17)
  - Huron County Public Library, 1985 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hyman, Stanley, 1957 (Box Series I-17)
  - Hymes, Dell (Box Series I-17)
  - Illinois State Museum, 1944 (Box Series I-17)
  - Independence National Historic Park, 1989 (Box Series I-17)
  - Indian Association of Alberta, 1986 (Box Series I-17)
    Staatliches Museum fur Volkerkund
    van Tilborg, John W.R.
  - Indian Historian, 1969-1971 (Box Series I-17)
    Henry, Jeanette
  - Indian Rights Association (Box Series I-17)
  - The Indian Trader, 1977 (Box Series I-17)
  - Indiana University, 1956-1993 (Box Series I-17)
  - Indians at Work, 1936 (Box Series I-17)
  - Ingall, Gillian B., 1970 (Box Series I-17)
  - Inouye, Daniel K. (Box Series I-17)
  - Institute for Research in Social Sciences, 1967 (Box Series I-17)
  - Institute of Early American History and Culture, 1952-1984 (Box Series I-17)
    Butterfield, Lyman H.
    Cappon, Lester J.
  - Institute of Iroquoia, 1994 (Box Series I-17)
  - Institute of the American Indian and Alaska Native Culture and Arts Development (Box Series I-17)
  - Institute on Man and Science, 1968 (Box Series I-17)
  - International Committee for Social Sciences Documentation, 1956, 1958 (Box Series I-18)
  - International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences, 1962, 1971-1972 (Box Series I-18)
  - International Journal of American Linguistics, 1990 (Box Series I-18)
  - International Work Group for Indigenous Affairs (Box Series I-18)
    -See Ser. I, Ominayak, Bernard
  - Iowa Development Commission, 1965 (Box Series I-18)
  - Iroquoian Institute, 1990-1992 (Box Series I-18)
    Thomas, Jacob E.
    Thomas, Yvonne
  - Iroquois Indian Museum (Box Series I-18)
    -See Ser. I, Schoharie Museum of the Iroquois Indian
  - Irwin, Alfreda L., 1991 (Box Series I-18)
  - Isaacs, Avrom, 1993 (Box Series I-18)
  - Isaacs, Hope L., 1969-1976 (Box Series I-18)
  - Itschner, Emerson C. (Box Series I-18)
  - Iwanska, Alicja, 1969 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jacobs, Melville, 1940 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jacobs, Milton, 1969 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jacobs, Wilbur R., 1949, 1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jacobs, William, 1948, 1972, 1982 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jacobs Research Funds, 1987 (Box Series I-18)
    American Philosophical Society
    French, Kathrine S.
  - Jacobson, L., 1979 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jaenen, Cornelius J., 1980 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jamieson, Alex N., 1968-1970 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jamieson, Andrew, 1954 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jamieson, Mary, 1945 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jamieson, Sadie, 1943-1947, 1954 (Box Series I-18)
    Hill, Ike (Mrs.)
    Lewis, Susan
    -See also Ser. I, Lewis, Susan
  - Jamieson, Thomas J., 1949-1975, n.d. (Box Series I-18)
  - Jamnback, Hugo (Box Series I-18)
    -See Ser. I, Wykoff, M. William
  - Javits, Jacob K. (Box Series I-18)
    -See Ser. I, Hathorn, John R.
    -See Ser. I, Nash, Philleo
  - Jeanneret, André, 1966 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jenkins, Charles R., 1948-1949 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jenness, Diamond (Box Series I-18)
    -See Ser. I, National Museum of Canada
  - Jennings, Francis P. (Box Series I-18)
    Becker, Mary A. Druke
    -See also Ser. I, Becker, Mary A. Druke
    -See also Ser. I, Day, Gordon M.
    -See also Ser. I, Michelson, Gunther
    -See also Ser. IIa, Iroquois Documentary History Project
    - Folder #1, 1970-Jul. 1978 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #2, Sep. 1978-Mar. 1981 (Box Series I-18)
    - Folder #3, Apr. 1981-1992 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jennings, Jesse D., 1954 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jestreby, William, 1968 (Box Series I-18)
  - Jimerson, Avery, 1958 (Box Series I-18)
    -See also Ser. III, "In Memoriam: Harry Watt and Avery Jimerson"
  - Jimerson, Dan M. (Box Series I-18)
  - Jimerson, Tessie, 1941 (Box Series I-18)
  - Joffe, Natalie F., 1940 (Box Series I-18)
  - Johannsen, Christina B., 1984 (Box Series I-18)
    -See also Ser. I, Schoharie Museum of the Iroquois Indian
  - Johannsen, Uwe, 1991 (Box Series I-18)
  - John, Calvin, 1957, 1990 (Box Series I-19)
  - John, Franklin, 1950 (Box Series I-19)
  - John, William, 1944, 1947 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnny John, Richard, 1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1948-1949 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnson, Bruce B., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnson, C.E., 1971 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnson, Frederick, 1941, 1944 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Byers, Douglas S.
  - Johnson, Nancy, 1986 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnson, Thomas H., 1973 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnson, Willard F., 1968 (Box Series I-19)
  - Johnston, Charles M., 1962-1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Jones, Albert, 1933-1958 (Box Series I-19)
  - Jones, Earl, 1942 (Box Series I-19)
  - Jones, Geneva, 1967 (Box Series I-19)
  - Jones, Louis C., 1962, 1978 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Harrington, Mark Raymond
    -See also Ser. I, New York Folklore Society
  - Jones, Richard A. (Box Series I-19)
    -See Ser. I, Adirondack Conference Centers
  - Jones, Volney H., 1935, 1942 (Box Series I-19)
  - Jordan, Winifred, 1945-1946 (Box Series I-19)
  - Josephy, Alvin M., Jr., 1962, 1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Journal of American Folklore, 1942-1967 (Box Series I-19)
  - Journal of American History, 1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Journal of Higher Education, 1948 (Box Series I-19)
  - Judd, Neil M., 1959 (Box Series I-19)
  - Judkins, Russell A., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - July, Robert (Box Series I-19)
    -See Ser. I, Fagg, Bernard
  - Jury, Wilfrid, 1949 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kaberry, Phyllis M., 1943 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kadenbacher, Peter, 1980-1984 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kane, Albert G., 1947 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kanien'kehaka Raotitiohkwa Cultural Center, 1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kardos, James W., 1949 (Box Series I-19)
  - Katz, Paul R., 1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Katzer, Bruce, 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kazan, Elia, 1948, 1966 (Box Series I-19)
  - Keane, Martin J., 1989 (Box Series I-19)
  - Keating, Kenneth B., 1961 (Box Series I-19)
    Hayden, Carl
  - Kelley, Esther L., 1948 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kelly, Lawrence C., 1976-1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kelsay, Isabel T., 1975-1985 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kemper, Robert V., 1974 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kennard, Edward A., 1949 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kennedy, Hugh E., 1969 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box Series I-19)
    Williams, Basil
    -See also Ser. I, Morgan, Arthur E.
    -See also Ser. I, Taylor, Walter
    -See also Ser. I, Williams, Basil
  - Kennedy, Raymond, 1945 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1967 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kenny, Hamill, 1949 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kensinger, Kenneth M., 1989 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kent, Donald H., 1959-1979 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Pennsylvania Historical Commission
  - Keppler, Joseph, 1905-1944, n.d. (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Cornplanter, Edward
    -See also Ser. I, Logan, Frank
  - Kerstetter, Rose, 1984 (Box Series I-19)
  - Ketchum, Miriam B., 1948 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kiburtz, Louise, 1945 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kidd, Julie (Mrs. Wilmot H. III) (Box Series I-19)
  - Kidd, Kenneth E., 1942-1988 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Stewart, T.D.
  - Kidder, Alfred V. II, 1958-1967 (Box Series I-19)
    Cole, Fay-Cooper
    International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences
    Krader, Lawrence
    Tolstov, S.P.
    -See also Ser. I, Collins, Henry B.
    -See also Ser. I, Krader, Lawrence
  - Killian, Gerald, 1980 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kilpatrick, Jack Frederick, 1961-1964 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kimball, Solon T. (Box Series I-19)
    -See Ser. I, American Ethnological Society
    -See Ser. I, Watson, James B.
  - Kimura, Takeshi, 1994 (Box Series I-19)
  - King, Jeanne Snodgrass, 1963, 1991 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kinietz, Vernon, 1941 (Box Series I-19)
  - Klee, Linnea B., 1979 (Box Series I-19)
  - Klingbeil, Kurt, 1987 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kluckhohn, Clyde K.M., 1941-1960 (Box Series I-19)
  - Knoll, Charles M., 1946-1947, 1981 (Box Series I-19)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1945-1947, 1970 (Box Series I-19)
    Dichman, Louise
    Shugg, Roger W.
  - Knott, Sarah Gertrude, 1946 (Box Series I-19)
  - Knowles, Francis H.S., 1944-1952 (Box Series I-19)
  - Knowles, Kathleen, 1953 (Box Series I-19)
  - Koch, Edward, 1986 (Box Series I-19)
  - Koehler, Lyle, 1977 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, American Society for Ethnohistory
  - Koerner, Konrad (Box Series I-19)
    -See Ser. I, Cowan, William
    -See Ser. I, Foster, Michael K.
  - Kornblau, David L. (Box Series I-19)
    -See Ser. I, Costikyan, Edward N.
  - Korson, Rae, 1962 (Box Series I-19)
    -See also Ser. I, Library of Congress
  - Koster, Louis J., 1965 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kowiotoski, Stephen J., 1977 (Box Series I-19)
  - Krader, Lawrence, 1962-1970 (Box Series I-19)
  - Kraft, Herbert C., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-19)
  - Krakel, Dean, 1965 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kramer, Eugene F., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kraus, Bertram S., 1942 (Box Series I-20)
  - Krech, Shepard III, 1989 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kremans, Jack, 1940 (Box Series I-20)
  - Krickeberg, Walter, 1959 (Box Series I-20)
  - Krieger, H.W., 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kriendler, H. Peter, [1987] (Box Series I-20)
  - Kroeber, A[lfred] L., 1939, 1960 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kros, C.D. (Mrs.), 1972 (Box Series I-20)
  - Krusche, Rolf, 1977-1988 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kubie, Kenneth R., 1988 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kunitz, Stephen J., 1969 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch, 1947-1989, n.d. (Box Series I-20)
    Opler, Morris E.
  - Kurtz, Benjamin T., 1937 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kutsche, Paul, 1967 (Box Series I-20)
  - Kutz, David, 1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - LaBarre, Weston, 1949 (Box Series I-20)
  - La Fayette Teachers Association, 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - La France, Noah, 1940 (Box Series I-20)
  - La France, Ted, 1969 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lagarde-Blin, P.L., 1979 (Box Series I-20)
    in French
  - Laing, James L., 1950 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lally, T.J., 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lamalle, Edmond, 1971 (Box Series I-20)
    -See also Ser. I, Pouliot, Léon
  - Lamb, Gerald, 1982 (Box Series I-20)
    Seneca-Iroquois National Museum
  - Lamb, Trudie Ray, 1982 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lancaster County Library, 1980 (Box Series I-20)
  - Landsman, Gail H., 1988-1989 (Box Series I-20)
  - Landy, David, 1965 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lane, William T., 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Larson, Paul, 1981 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lasswell, Harold D., 1957-1958 (Box Series I-20)
  - Launer, Arden E. (Box Series I-20)
  - Launer, Philip J., 1977 (Box Series I-20)
    Launer, Arden E.
  - Layton, L.E., 1956 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lazarus, Arthur, Jr., 1960-1972 (Box Series I-20)
    Heron, George D.
    Morgan, Arthur E.
    Waters, Somerset R.
  - Leacock, Eleanor Burke, 1968, 1972 (Box Series I-20)
    Lurie, Nancy O.
    -See also Ser. I, Random House, Inc.
    -See also Ser. VI, Leacock, Eleanor Burke
  - LeBlanc, Peter G., 1965, 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Ledden, Millie, 1964 (Box Series I-20)
    Munby, A. N. L.
  - Leder, Lawrence, 1964 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lee, Alfred McClung, 1945-1946 (Box Series I-20)
    -See also Ser. I, Zahniser, Howard
  - Lee, Chauncey, 1934 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lee, Nina, 1969 (Box Series I-20)
    Hathorn, John
  - Leechman, Douglas, 1947, 1957 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lehman, Edward J. (Box Series I-20)
    -See Ser. I, American Anthropological Society
  - Lehman, Jane B., 1986 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lemay, J.A. Leo, 1971 (Box Series I-20)
  - Leslie, John F., 1977 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lessa, Bill, 1969 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lessard, Rosemary, 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lévi-Strauss, Claude, 1967-1976 (Box Series I-20)
  - Levy, Wayne L., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Clifford, 3rd, 1950, 1972-1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Clifford M., 1949-1950 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Diane K., 1970 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Ida, 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Malcolm W., 1946 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Oscar, 1949 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Ralph H. (Box Series I-20)
  - Lewis, Susan, 1945 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lex, Barbara W., 1974 (Box Series I-20)
  - Libby, Dorothy, 1965 (Box Series I-20)
  - Liberty, Margot (Box Series I-20)
  - Library-Anthropology Resource Group, 1988 (Box Series I-20)
  - Library of Congress, 1943-1992 (Box Series I-20)
    Korson, Rae
    Logan, Joseph, Jr.
    Spivacke, Harold
    Taylor, Walter
  - Lickers, Huron, 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lickers, Sam, 1943 (Box Series I-20)
  - Liddle, Nancy (Box Series I-20)
  - Liesinger, Rudolph O., 1956 (Box Series I-20)
  - Liggett & Myers Tobacco Co., 1941 (Box Series I-20)
  - Light, Robert M., 1957 (Box Series I-20)
  - Liljeblad, Sven, 1945 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lillard, Richard G., 1946 (Box Series I-20)
  - Linck, Dana C., 1968 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lindig, Wolfgang, 1962 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lindley, Franklyn C., 1962 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lindsay, G. Carroll, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box Series I-20)
    Riposo, Nancy
    -See also Ser. I, Riposo, Nancy
  - Lindsey, Edward, 1942 (Box Series I-20)
    Noon, John A.
  - Linton, Ralph, 1943-1948 (Box Series I-20)
  - Lips, Eva, 1962-1970 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lismer, Marjorie (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Bridges, Marjorie Lismer
  - Little, Brown and Company, 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - Livingston, Katherine S., 1970 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lobsinger-Dellenbach, Marguerite, 1963 (Box Series I-21)
  - Locher, Godfried W., 1963 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lodder, Grace B., 1945-1946 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lodder, William, 1963 (Box Series I-21)
  - Loewenberg, Sarah, 1968 (Box Series I-21)
  - Logan, Aldephena, 1968 (Box Series I-21)
    Cayuga County Historical Society
  - Logan, Frank, 1906, 1942 (Box Series I-21)
  - Logan, Joseph, 1942 (Box Series I-21)
  - Logan, Joseph, Jr. (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Library of Congress
  - Lomax, Alan, n.d. (Box Series I-21)
  - Long, Joseph K., 1973 (Box Series I-21)
  - Long, Walter K. (Box Series I-21)
  - Longboat, Thomas C., 1985, 1988 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lookaround, Angus F. (Mrs.), 1946 (Box Series I-21)
  - Loring, Stephen, 1993 (Box Series I-21)
    Fitzhugh, William
  - Lothrop, Francis Bacon, 1961-1962 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lounsbury, Floyd G., 1941-1974 (Box Series I-21)
    Miller, P. Schuyler
  - Lowenthal, Max (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Cosmos Club
  - Lowie, Robert H., 1949, 1953 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lowie Museum of Anthropology (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Avirom, Don
  - Lucas, H.W., 1946 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lucas, Jack A., 1982 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lucy, Charles L., 1947-1988, n.d. (Box Series I-21)
    Randle, Martha Champion
    -See also Ser. I, Deskaheh, Chief
    -See also Ser. I, Fadden, Ray
    -See also Ser. I, Wallace, Anthony F.C.
    -See also Ser. IV, Lucy, Charles L., Iroquois Lacrosse--Research
  - Lunde, Anders S., 1987 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lurie, Edward, 1953 (Box Series I-21)
    Rubey, William W.
  - Lurie, Nancy Oestreich, 1944-1992 (Box Series I-21)
    -See also Ser. I, Central States Anthropological Society
    -See also Ser. I, Leacock, Eleanor Burke
  - Luth, Dietrich, 1968 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lynch, James P., 1981-1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Lynd, Robert S., 1944 (Box Series I-21)
  - MPO Film Distribution Co., 1956 (Box Series I-21)
    Sehmert, Marion P.
  - McAllester, David P., 1969 (Box Series I-21)
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1990 (Box Series I-21)
  - MacCallum, Spencer H., 1971-1972 (Box Series I-21)
    Historical Society of Pennsylvania
  - McCann, Catherine, 1962 (Box Series I-21)
  - McCarthy, Richard L., 1955-1956 (Box Series I-21)
  - McClenahan, Bill, 1945 (Box Series I-21)
  - McCrum, Blanche Prichard (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Bailey, Alfred G.
  - McDermott, Patricia (Box Series I-21)
  - McDonald, Dorothy, 1992 (Box Series I-21)
  - McElroy, W. Proctor, 1943 (Box Series I-21)
  - MacFarlan, Allan A., 1967 (Box Series I-21)
  - McFarland, Alex J. (Box Series I-21)
  - McFeat, Tom F.S., 1985-1989 (Box Series I-21)
  - McGee, Dorothy H. (Box Series I-21)
    -See Ser. I, Brasser, Ted J.
  - McGill, Alan, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - McGill, Robert A., 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - McGill-Queen's University Press, 1984-1987 (Box Series I-21)
  - McGovern, Joseph W., 1968 (Box Series I-21)
  - MacGowan, Kenneth, 1957 (Box Series I-21)
  - McIlwraith, Thomas F., 1939-1962, 1992 (Box Series I-21)
    -See also Ser. I, Royal Canadian Institute
  - McKay, Donald C., 1945, 1950 (Box Series I-21)
  - McKennan, Robert A., 1942-1965 (Box Series I-21)
    -See also Ser. I, Holmes, Harry A.
  - McKinley, Daniel, 1969 (Box Series I-21)
  - McLean, Dorothy, 1954 (Box Series I-21)
  - MacLean, Hugh, 1985 (Box Series I-21)
  - Macmillan, Robert, 1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Macmillan Company Publishers, 1941-1953, 1972 (Box Series I-21)
  - McMullen, Ann, 1990 (Box Series I-21)
  - McMullen, Vincent, 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - MacMurtrie, Frances Fenton, 1939-1945, 1975 (Box Series I-21)
    MacMurtrie, George C.
  - MacMurtrie, George C., 1944 (Box Series I-21)
    -See also Ser. I, MacMurtrie, Frances
  - McNickle, D'Arcy, 1968, 1975 (Box Series I-21)
  - McNulty, Michael R., 1992 (Box Series I-21)
  - McPhee, Colin, 1946 (Box Series I-21)
  - Madigan, LaVerne, 1957 (Box Series I-21)
    Association on American Indian Affairs, Inc.
  - Mahoney, Charles L., 1971 (Box Series I-21)
  - Mair, Heidi L., 1984, 1986 (Box Series I-21)
  - Malinowski, B., 1933 (Box Series I-21)
  - Mallery, A.H., 1941-1946 (Box Series I-21)
  - Mallonee, Keith, 1974 (Box Series I-21)
  - Mandelbaum, David G., 1941-1968 (Box Series I-21)
    Ray, Verne F.
  - Man in the Northeast, 1990 (Box Series I-21)
  - Manley, Henry S., 1950, 1958 (Box Series I-21)
    -See also Ser. I, Tyrell, William G.
  - Manning, Roy O., 1968 (Box Series I-21)
  - Mariella, Patricia S., 1979 (Box Series I-22)
  - Marsh, Mike, 1970 (Box Series I-22)
  - Marshall, Alton G., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-22)
    Rockefeller, Nelson
    Weisman, Abner I.
  - Marshall, Ingeborg, 1981 (Box Series I-22)
  - Marshall, John (Box Series I-22)
    -See Ser. I, Rockefeller Foundation
  - Martijn, Charles A., 1985 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, A. (Mrs.), 1942-1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, Alan, 1943 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, Barry J., 1980 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, Calvin, 1988 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, Edward (Box Series I-22)
    -See Ser. I, Wetmore, A.
  - Martin, Marlene, 1969-1990 (Box Series I-22)
  - Martin, William Cabot, 1946 (Box Series I-22)
  - Marye, William B., 1945 (Box Series I-22)
  - Mason, J. Alden, 1950 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, American Anthropologist
    -See also Ser. I, Philadelphia Anthropological Society
  - Mason, Max W., 1941 (Box Series I-22)
    -See also Ser. I, Mason, Roy M.
  - Mason, Roy M., 1941 (Box Series I-22)
    Mason, Max W.
  - Massachusetts Archives, 1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1961, 1964 (Box Series I-22)
  - Masse, Ed, 1939 (Box Series I-22)
  - Massicot, William L. (Mrs.), 1949 (Box Series I-22)
  - Masthay, Carl, 1982 (Box Series I-22)